question_data = [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "In the Greek Mythology, the Gorgon can turn those who behold her to stone.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "A wyvern is the same as a dragon.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "In the Greek Mythology, the god of war is called Mars.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "The Roman god 'Jupiter' was first known as 'Zeus' to the Greeks.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "Skadi is the Norse Goddess of skiing, mountains, winter and bowhunting.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]